https://70birds.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy - 70birds
HomeBirdsBirdhousesBirdhouse PlansBird FeedersCity BirdsBirdhouse ForumHow toAbout
Select Page
Privacy Policy 70birds Discussion Forum If visitors choose to register on the 70birds discussion forum, a forum software collects and stores information from users such as user name, password, email address, IP address. This information is used to verify registered forum users when they log in. IP addresses may be used to ban registered forum users who post spam or other objectionable material. None of this information is shared or made available to anyone.Comment Form Visitors who use the comment form to send messages to 70birds administrators are not required to provide contact information or identify themselves.Advertisements Visitors who select advertisements will likely be directed to third-party vendor’s websites where cookies will likely be installed on visitors’ browsers. Below is information regarding cookies from third-party vendors:Important Information About Google’s Uses of Personal Data – How Google uses information from sites or apps that use their services – Ad personalization – How to control information collected by Google on these sites and apps. Read MoreAdditional Third-Party Vendors Web users who select product advertisements to examine those products, may be directed to other third-party vendor’s websites. When users visit other third-party vendor’s websites, a cookie may be dropped on that end user’s browser. Users may examine the privacy policies of third-party vendor’s at those websites. Additionally, users can opt out of some, but not all, of these third-party vendor cookies at the Network Advertising Initiative opt-out website: http://optout.networkadvertising.org/?c=1#!/
Facebook
Twitter
Google
RSS Designed by Elegant Themes | Powered by WordPress
We at 70birds have no interest in your information. Nevertheless, cookies are needed to support some applications such as a discussion forum and social share ability. See 70birds Privacy Policy If you select an advertisement to view another party's product website, their use of cookies should be explained in their cookie notice and/or privacy policy. Ok
